<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-07T18:43:26+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Beat</title><subtitle>BEAT is a celebration of each of us and all of us at once. It’s an opportunity to reflect, engage, explore, inspire and connect. Using workshops, games, conversations and storytelling to strengthen our relationships and share our knowledge. It only works if we all work. We get out of it what we put into it. This isn’t a conference. It isn’t a summit. This is a chance to take a BEAT.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">register</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sign_up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="register" /><published>2017-10-03T12:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-10-03T12:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sign_up</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sign_up.html">&lt;div style=&quot;height: 10vw;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;big-links&quot; href=&quot;https://voxproduct.typeform.com/to/EGJWFB&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;big-links&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;a class=&quot;big-links&quot; href=&quot;http://bit.ly/2hM71DE&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;book hotel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;section class=&quot;c-post--list&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;Logistics&quot; id=&quot;log&quot;&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;When is BEAT?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;January 25th - 26th&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Wednesday January 24th: check-in for out of towners&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Thursday January 25th: 9am - 5pm &amp;amp; evening dinner/activities&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Friday January 26th: 9am - 3pm&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Where is BEAT&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thelinehotel.com/dc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Line Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Meals at BEAT&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;All meals will be catered by the Line Hotel and will incorporate dietary requests and preferences. The food and beverage programs at the hotel are run by Spike Gjerde, Corey Polyoka, Todd Thrasher and Erik Bruner-Yang. I think we’ll eat and drink &lt;a href=&quot;https://dc.eater.com/2016/4/11/11406188/line-hotel-restaurants-erik-bruner-yang-spike-gjerde&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;okay&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;We will have a team dinner on Thursday evening that will finish by 9pm.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Travel &amp;amp; Board at BEAT&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you are traveling to D.C. please use PRO750 when booking via Egencia.
  If you plan to drive, please mention that in registration and include the requested information.
  Please book your hotel room on the registration page using the booking link provided. If you are willing and/or interested in rooming with someone, please indicate that in the booking link.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;If you live in DC or the great DMV area, staying at the hotel is optional. We are happy to reimburse your travel expenses whether they are bus, metro, taxi or parking expenses should you forgo staying with us.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;How do I prepare for Beat?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Read through this site in its entirety
  Go to the “Sign Up” section and book your hotel and fill out the sign-up form.
  Book your travel (if applicable) via Egencia using PRO710. Do this ASAP!
  Head to the “Curate” page to start submitting your contributions.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Participant Timeline&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;By December 1 make sure all of your contributions have been uploaded to the “Curate” Trello Board.
  In December, Ashley will start to work her scheduling magic and notify participants whether or not they’ll be presenting. She’ll also announce
  A near-final agenda will come together by end of December and be posted to the site.
  Explanations of how to prepare/get organized/choose your schedule will come in early January.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">about</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/about.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="about" /><published>2017-10-02T12:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-10-02T12:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/about</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/about.html">&lt;div style=&quot;height: 10vw;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;heading-links&quot; id=&quot;participant&quot; href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Participant Guide&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;section class=&quot;c-post--list&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;participant&quot; id=&quot;part&quot;&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;What is BEAT?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BEAT&lt;/strong&gt; is a celebration of each of us and all of us at once. It’s an opportunity to reflect, engage, explore, inspire and connect. Using workshops, games, conversations and storytelling to strengthen our relationships and share our knowledge. It only works if we all work. We get out of it what we put into it. This isn’t a conference. It isn’t a summit. This is a chance to take a BEAT.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;At its core, BEAT is an “unconference” in the sense that the content is decided by the participants. Topics may include industry related information, skill-building, and culture sharing. Formats include workshops, small conversations and storytelling/lightning talks. Additionally we’ll have some conversation from leadership and open office hours that you can book. We also want to welcome outside guest speakers, called “+1s”, to provide keynote speeches or workshops on topics you pick.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;How is BEAT different than AFK?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;To date we’ve had three AFKs. The first was at a campsite in the Shenandoah Valley, the second followed the 2016 Chicago VAX and the third was a design team retreat. We’ve had lots of variations of format, style and purpose for AFK, so we wanted to create a clear delineation between the two. BEAT is our answer to a team all-hands that was normally covered within the timeline of VAX, but unsuccessfully due to time constraints.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Do I have to use ProDev to attend BEAT?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;No, Vox Media is covering the costs for BEAT and we’re extremely grateful they’ve allowed us to do this.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;This is a “Vox Product” event but I’m embedded into another team; can I still attend?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yes, all product, design and technology team members may attend. If you have questions about someone’s participation, reach out directly to Ashley to ask.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Will there be space for me to take a break and recharge?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yes, there will be designated quiet areas as well as lengthier break times. Additionally, if you wish to take a longer break from programming, you may do so.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Is BEAT mandatory?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;While BEAT is not mandatory, it is highly encouraged. Trust us, the FOMO will be real, so we hope you’ll plan to join us.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Do you cover childcare costs during the event?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately no. We are not at the scale to be able to cover childcare costs for any work or team related events. I hope with enough advanced planning you are able to find coverage and join us!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Will the content be recorded?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We haven’t decided yet. This will be based on the topics and capabilities to do so. TL;DR, it might not be pretty and therefore, not worthwhile. If you have suggestions on this, let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

  &lt;h2&gt;Do I have to “contribute” to BEAT? What if I don’t have anything to share or get anxiety speaking to large groups?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Whether you believe us or not, you definitely have something to contribute or you wouldn’t be here! Everyone on our team has unique talents and interests or things that you’re learning more about and want to share! We won’t have time to hear from everyone, however, we encourage you to at least apply. Additionally, if you’re a little shy, you could also propose a post-dinner activity like a board game you love. Even if you don’t host something, attitude is everything; plan to come as an active and engaged participant!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1cQQ467zCs549MMVEEhFT0T9xTx4KJWNwFjOqFTK8N-8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here are some examples of what you might be able to host.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;break&gt;&lt;/break&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>